When starting out in this industry it can be very daunting because you're not
really
sure what to say or what to do and that's why we are here.
So the first thing that we would say is to complete our online training courses
as in
there there is so much information that will make you feel so empowered and so
knowledgeable
and so ready to just get started.
When starting out on webcam you can either be yourself and that means you can
get playful
and be creative with yourself and who you want to be on cam or you can develop
an alter ego
and we're here to give you plenty of inspiration from our website and from your
fellow webcam
models on what that might look like.
Another good thing to note is to ask open questions and if a client comes into
your room and asks
you something that you don't know you can just ask them, your clients
absolutely love
to teach you and especially when you're new you can really play on this and
play the new
card for as long as possible because they love to feel like they're really
helping you
on your new journey.
Remember that webcam is a fantasy and you are totally in control so anything
that you
talk about doesn't mean that you have to do it, it's pure fantasy and you can
stop the
call, kick somebody out of your room or just walk away at any time.
From the outside I think a lot of people have opinions and expectations of what
a webcam
model is or what she does or what she looks like but that is not the case.
There are so many different avenues you can take this down.
You don't have to just be the typical webcam model because there's not even one
.
You can go down and do domination, you could be a sub, you could be the girl
next door,
you could do taboo, there's so many different things you could do, you can even
just play
the girlfriend's experience and just chat and type with your client and you don
't ever
have to perform or do anything that you don't feel comfortable with.
Remember that every single webcam model including us started not knowing what
to do or say
with those first day nerves.
If you just log on with this supportive community behind you, you can't go
wrong.
You